gayishmovies.com 2017-12-02

# Privacy - Gay.Sex.com

Effective February 2012

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of Gay.Sex.com. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the site. This Privacy Policy may be updated on occasion. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes.

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over, or having attained the age of majority in their country. All persons who do not meet this criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

The security of your Data is very important to Gay.Sex.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

## DATA COLLECTED

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our site, application, services, features and content, to administer your membership and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the site.

Personal Information:

  * Non-Registered users can watch pictures & videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. However, the visitor's IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.
  * Registered Members: Registration is required for uploading pictures & videos, and accessing a number of other features. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), and email address (required). All of this data, with the exception of the email address and IP address, becomes publicly accessible information.

Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information or picture/video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

Cookies: When you visit Gay.Sex.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. Gay.Sex.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.

Log File Information: When you visit Gay.Sex.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

## USES

The personally identifiable information you submit to Gay.Sex.com is used to provide you as the user with special, personalized site features.

Your chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including pictures & videos, comments, likes, etc.

Any picture or videos that you submit to Gay.Sex.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

We may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages.

We may use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).

Opt-in communication — Subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his/her email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him/her offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with the option to express the subscriber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes", the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information, including its email address and data may be used for that matter."

Opt-out communication — Subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his/her email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may not be used to send him/her offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications.

We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the Gay.Sex.com user-experience.

## DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

If required to do so, Gay.Sex.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of Gay.Sex.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms of Service. It is Gay.Sex.com's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.

Should you deliberately upload any illegal material, Gay.Sex.com shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and do so without notice.

We do not share your personally identifiable information, such as email address, with other third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent, or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Our site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## SECURITY

Here we have given you, or you have chosen, a password, which enables you to access certain parts of our Site. You are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Gay.Sex.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Gay.Sex.com, and you do so at your own risk.

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to us. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission's website.

## YOUR RIGHTS

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the personal information in their account by contacting us or by editing said profile via the site. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

## CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at:
